grandmajuice.net 2015-06-05

# This Privacy Policy Is In Effect For The Grandma Juice Website

**0** Flares Twitter 0 Facebook 0 Google+ 0 StumbleUpon 0 Reddit 0 Email \-- **0** Flares ×

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or Enter a Giveaway.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may however, of course, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, _**will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent**_ , other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

 _ **We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information**_. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. _**We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent**_.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 6/19/2012

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.grandmajuice.net  
info@grandmajuice.net

This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm) authority.
